TianoCore UDK2019 Build Instructions for Intel(R) ice Open Source Driver
Copyright 2016-2021, Intel Corporation, All Rights Reserved


PREBUILD INSTRUCTIONS
---------------------
The files included in this source package allow the ice UEFI UNDI driver binary to be built as part of the Tiano Core UDK2019 source tree. Before building the driver you must download the Tiano Core UDK2019 release source from www.tianocore.org and follow the instructions in Release Notes to build the tree for your target architecture.

Note: Extract the contents of BaseTools(Windows).zip directly to the directory with the package folders.


BUILD INSTRUCTIONS
------------------
These instructions use the Microsoft Visual Studio 15 (2017) compiler tools.
Follow the below steps to integrate the ice UEFI UNDI driver into the UDK2019 source tree.

1. Extract the contents of iceUndiDxe.zip into the UDK2019 root/workspace directory so that "IntelUndiPkg" and "MyStdLib" folders are placed among the other "Pkg" folders.

2. Change to the root directory and run edksetup.bat to set up a workspace environment for UDK2019.

3. Provide architecture, toolchain, package to build, module and build type as parameters to build the UEFI driver executable. Supported architectures are:
A32 and X64.
For example, to build for the IA32 architecture:

build -a IA32 -t VS2017x86 -p IntelUndiPkg\InteliceUndiPkg.dsc -m IntelUndiPkg\iceUndiDxe\iceUndiDxe.inf -b RELEASE

4. The resultant .efi image is located in:
\Build\IntelUndiPkg\RELEASE_{TOOLCHAIN}\{ARCHITECTURE}\iceUndiDxe.efi
depending on target toolchain and architecture.


Trademarks
==========
Intel is a trademark or registered trademark of Intel Corporation or its subsidiaries in the United States and/or other countries.

* Other names and brands may be claimed as the property of others.


